<aiml>
  <category>
    <pattern>I want to talk about *</pattern>
    <template><set topic = "topic"><star /></set></template>
  </category>
  
  <topic nTopic="potato-district">
    <category>
      <pattern>How was the Potato District created?</pattern>
      <template>The potato district started out as a city sized bomb shelter during the war between Japanese and French controlled American colonies.</template>
    </category>
    
    <category>
      <pattern>What are those giant bladed projectile weapons?</pattern>
      <template>You must be referring to the National Razor Crossbow. That evolved from the Berger guillotine. Initially it was a rolling model sort of like a gatling gun, or that giant Roman crossbow. But eventually it was shrunk down to the size of a personal melee weapon. It shoots out a guillotine blade. It used to be used as an execution method, but became a standard self-defence weapon.</template>
    </category>
    
    <category>
      <pattern>Why have they not clamped down on National Razor Crossbow posession?</pattern>
      <template>In general attempting to reposess them would just cause more revolutions, and doing more harm than good. Although there is a definite difference between the kind your average civilian has and an infrantry man or militarized cop. Our can only shoot one guillotine blade at a time, but cops and police are permitted to store multiple blades at a time, using an assistant to fire them.</template>
    </category>
    
    <category>
      <pattern>What is your national landmark?</pattern>
      <template>The landmark of my nation is Ruby Falls. There is also a place in my city that's a cave, where you can find Brother's Grim statues.</template>
    </cateogry>
  </topic>
    
  <topic nTopic="personal-matters">
    <cateogry>
      <pattern>Who was your mother?</pattern>
      <template>Mother was a career politician that assisted in managerial work, although when she was around I did not know this at the time.</template>
    </cateogry>
    
    <category>
      <pattern>Why did you move to a reform school?</pattern>
      <category>I was perpetually late to class, and had a tendency to be literally thrown off the flying wing bus.</category>
    </category>
    
    <category>
      <pattern>What is that robot you are building?</pattern>
      <template>I'm still trying to finish working on my robotic dog, although this had been delayed slightly.</template>
    </category>
  </topic>
</aiml>
